secondspin.com 2011-03-06

# SecondSpin.com

At SecondSpin.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We firmly believe that electronic security and privacy are necessary for the continued success of the Internet as an entertainment medium. In support of this, we will only use the personal information that you provide us in accordance with the terms outlined below. BY VISITING SECONDSPIN.COM, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY NOTICE. 

**Scope** **  
** Although selling, and exchanging on SecondSpin.com is currently limited to residents of the United States, Canada and the United Kingdom this privacy policy applies to all site visitors, regardless of their nation of residence.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Passwords and orders are collected through and stored on secure servers. Paper records of financial transactions are stored in a locked facility. Our members' personal information will not be sold or given out, except as specifically authorized or when required by law.

**General Policy**  
We reserve the right to refuse service, terminate accounts or cancel orders at our discretion.

Trans World Entertainmenet Corporation  
Attn: SecondSpin.com  
900 N. Rohlwing Rd.  
Itasca, IL 60143  

**SecondSpin.com's Personal Information Gathering Practices**

SecondSpin.com actively collects information from its members to allow us to operate our site. Such information includes member first and last names, billing and shipping addresses, day and evening phone numbers, date of birth, credit card numbers and e-mail addresses. We collect this information when members complete registration.

Additionally, SecondSpin.com utilizes "cookies" to track our members through their user sessions, collecting information on user tastes and preferences. This information is not sold or shared with others, and is solely used to provide SecondSpin.com users with a better online experience. SecondSpin.com does not use cookies to track user activities beyond their use of SecondSpin.com's service.

SecondSpin.com does not and will not sell customer information to any third party. In the event that SecondSpin.com should merge with, acquire, or be acquired by another business entity, SecondSpin.com would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide you with full and complete service.

**Registration**  
Our site registration form requires that users provide us with contact information, including their name, home address, and email address; billing information, including a credit card number; and demographic information including zip codes and birth dates. We use this information for contact and billing purposes and to administer accounts when a user requests assistance.

**Contest Participation**  
SecondSpin.com sponsors contests in which visitors may be asked to supply us with contact information. This information is required for contest notifications. Users may opt-out of receiving further information regarding contests at any time. Please see Choice/Opt-out Section below.

**Third Party Content** **  
** SecondSpin.com contains content from and links to other web sites. We provide outlets to other sites in order to deliver a more complete entertainment experience. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, SecondSpin.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site. If you have comments or concerns regarding the content of a third party site, please contact the web administrator of that site.

**Cookies**  
At SecondSpin.com, we must use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to administer our web site and identify users. We use cookies as a means to track and store information gathered from IP addresses. Additionally, cookies allow us to track user behavior and preferences. SecondSpin.com only tracks user activity on SecondSpin.com's website through cookies.

**Consent**  
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SecondSpin.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**A Special Note About Children Under 13** **  
** SecondSpin.com recognizes the importance of keeping children safe in cyberspace. We encourage parents and guardians to be aware of the nature of the sites their children visit, and to participate in their children's online experiences.

In accordance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), children under the age of 13 are not allowed to register as members of SecondSpin.com.

_As a Parent, What Does this Mean to You?_  
As a practical matter, you do not need to be a member of SecondSpin.com to enjoy our great content. Under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator can require, as a condition of participation in an activity, that a child under the age of 13 disclose more information than is reasonably necessary. SecondSpin.com abides by this requirement. We do not request, nor do we collect, any personally identifying information from non-members in order to use these features of our site. While children of all ages are welcome to visit our site to enjoy these features, parents and guardians should note that while SecondSpin.com is primarily a general interest web site with content suitable for everyone, some material on our site (features dealing with "R" rated movies and explicit lyrics in music, for example) may be inappropriate for children.

However, we do use personal member information for site personalization features and for the administration of our sweepstakes, games and contests. Accordingly, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting verifiable parental consent. Since we require users to provide some personal information to register for SecondSpin.com membership before they may use these site personalization features and services, children under 13 will not be able to use these features of our site WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF, AND USE OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION BY, WEBSITES THAT WE DON'T OPERATE, and this policy does not apply to linked sites

**SecondSpin.com's Personal Information Usage Practices**  
SecondSpin.com intends to use members' personal information for site related activities, to notify contest winners, and for delivering internal newsletters.

The following describes the means by which SecondSpin.com uses personal information gathered on our site:

**Electronic Newsletter Mailings**  
SecondSpin.com uses a member's e-mail address for electronic newsletter mailings to those who've asked to receive these mailings. SecondSpin.com maintains a member mailing list with opt-in information and from time to time sends a site newsletter via e-mail. During the registration process, members are informed about these mailings and can give permission to receive them. See the Choice/Opt-Out section below to change your permissions.

**Sharing information with others**  
We may share information with our promotional partners and sponsors, if you've agreed, in order to bring you special offers and information. In addition, we sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, consolidating customer information, and analyzing data. They may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use this information for any other purposes.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications at any time. Requests for opting-out of mailings should be sent to [customerservice@secondspin.com](mailto:customerservice@secondspin.com). 

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives registered users the ability to easily change or modify personally identifiable information previously provided. To do so, Log In and visit the My Account page.
